(Penny:)the order is petting zoo first,
then buy vegetables.
(Raj:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good. You're here.
I need your assistance.
(Leonard:)Can it wait until I put
a Band-Aid on a goat bite?
(Sheldon:)What happened?
Oh.
(Penny:)Your buddy got mugged
by some baby farm animals.
(Sheldon:)Been there.
Mmm.
(Penny:)So what do you need help with?
(Sheldon:)Amy's mad at me,
and I'm not clear why.
(Penny:)Okay. Were you talking
before she got upset?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
That's probably it.
(Penny:)What'd you say to her?
(Sheldon:)Well, I just asked her
if I should start watching
the new Flash TV series.
(Penny:)And that made her angry?
(Sheldon:)Baffling, right? We were necking
(Sheldon:)like a couple of hooligans
under the school bleachers.
(Sheldon:)I stopped so I could ask
the question.
(Sheldon:)Next thing I know, good-bye,
kissy face. Hello, yelly face.
(Penny:)Well, Sheldon, when
you're kissing a girl,
(Penny:)she expects the
attention to be on her.
(Sheldon:)It was. I asked her
if she thought
I should watch The Flash.